[Music]
Hello and welcome to What's Cooking. In
this video, we're showing you a thing
that we're cooking up to assist users
working with agents and AI. First, for
the payable agent in the 2025 wave 2
major release and potentially for other
features down the road.
For users to adopt AI, it's important
that they trust AI. Therefore, we're
surfacing the payables agents reasoning
to the user so they know why the agent
suggested a certain field value. So,
what we're looking at here is the is a
purchase document draft where the we
have imported one invoice with one line
on it. And in this case, the agent
suggests a GL account. And you'll now
notice the small I icon next to the
account number. And this is where we're
surfacing the agent's reasoning. So I
can click that and I can now see why
does the agent think this account from
the chart of accounts is the best match
for this type of expense.
But you notice here it says two fields
for review. So there must be one more
field here that I need to review. So if
I browse a bit, scroll a bit to the
right, I can see the deferral code. It's
actually been set to one Y. So I would
think that's one year. Let's see the
reasoning for that.
Actually here we see that there's a nice
reasoning for why it thinks I need to
use a default code and it will find the
default code itself. So this way we want
to show how the agent uh gets to a
certain field value and this goes
regardless if it suggest counts or an
item uses item references whatever it
does. So this is important for users to
trust and learn how to work with AI.
Thank you.